<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EquipmentReliability on Kaiser Blog</title>
    <link>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/tags/equipmentreliability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in EquipmentReliability on Kaiser Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:38:05 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/tags/equipmentreliability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Preventive Maintainance</title>
      <link>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/preventive_maintainace/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:38:05 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/preventive_maintainace/</guid>
      <description>What is Preventive Maintainance? Preventive maintenance is the act of performing regularly scheduled maintenance activities to help prevent unexpected failures in the future. Put simply, it’s about fixing things before they break.&#xA;Why is preventive maintenance important? Preventive maintenance is important because it lays the foundation for successful facility management. Preventive maintenance keeps equipment and assets running efficiently, maintains a high safety level for your employees, and helps you avoid large and costly repairs down the road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictive Maintainance</title>
      <link>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/predictive_maintainace/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:33:47 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/predictive_maintainace/</guid>
      <description>What is predictive maintenance (PdM)? Predictive maintenance (PdM) uses data analysis to identify operational anomalies and potential equipment defects, enabling timely repairs before failures occur. It aims to minimize maintenance frequency, avoiding unplanned outages and unnecessary preventive maintenance costs.&#xA;When is predictive maintenance suitable? Suitable applications Applications that are suitable for predictive maintenance (PdM) include those that:&#xA;Have a critical operational function Have failure modes that can be cost-effectively predicted with regular monitoring Unsuitable applications Unsuitable applications for predictive maintenance include those that:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
