<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on Kaiser Blog</title>
    <link>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on Kaiser Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:38:05 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Preventive Maintainance</title>
      <link>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/preventive_maintainace/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:38:05 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/preventive_maintainace/</guid>
      <description>What is Preventive Maintainance? Preventive maintenance is the act of performing regularly scheduled maintenance activities to help prevent unexpected failures in the future. Put simply, it’s about fixing things before they break.&#xA;Why is preventive maintenance important? Preventive maintenance is important because it lays the foundation for successful facility management. Preventive maintenance keeps equipment and assets running efficiently, maintains a high safety level for your employees, and helps you avoid large and costly repairs down the road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictive Maintainance</title>
      <link>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/predictive_maintainace/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 23:33:47 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/predictive_maintainace/</guid>
      <description>What is predictive maintenance (PdM)? Predictive maintenance (PdM) uses data analysis to identify operational anomalies and potential equipment defects, enabling timely repairs before failures occur. It aims to minimize maintenance frequency, avoiding unplanned outages and unnecessary preventive maintenance costs.&#xA;When is predictive maintenance suitable? Suitable applications Applications that are suitable for predictive maintenance (PdM) include those that:&#xA;Have a critical operational function Have failure modes that can be cost-effectively predicted with regular monitoring Unsuitable applications Unsuitable applications for predictive maintenance include those that:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage common threats, risks, and vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/security/manage_common_threads_risks_and_vulnerabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 01:05:06 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/security/manage_common_threads_risks_and_vulnerabilities/</guid>
      <description>Risk management A primary goal of organizations is to protect assets. An asset is an item perceived as having value to an organization. Assets can be digital or physical. Examples of digital assets include the personal information of employees, clients, or vendors, such as:&#xA;Social Security Numbers (SSNs), or unique national identification numbers assigned to individuals Dates of birth Bank account numbers Mailing addresses Examples of physical assets include:&#xA;Payment kiosks Servers Desktop computers Office spaces Some common strategies used to manage risks include:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security domains cybersecurity analysts need to know</title>
      <link>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/security/need_to_know/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 23:17:11 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/security/need_to_know/</guid>
      <description>Domain one: Security and risk management All organizations must develop their security posture. Security posture is an organization’s ability to manage its defense of critical assets and data and react to change. Elements of the security and risk management domain that impact an organization&amp;rsquo;s security posture include:&#xA;Security goals and objectives Risk mitigation processes Compliance Business continuity plans Legal regulations Professional and organizational ethics Information security, or InfoSec, is also related to this domain and refers to a set of processes established to secure information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Palette Storage</title>
      <link>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/material/color_pallete/color_pallete/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 23:01:58 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/material/color_pallete/color_pallete/</guid>
      <description>Rainbow Pastel Color Palettes Rainbow Color Value Remark #FAEDCB #C9E4DE #C6DEF1 #DBCDF0 #F2C6DE #F7D9C4 Technicolor Color Value Remark #FFADAD #FFD6A5 #FDFFB6 #E4F1EE #D9EDF8 #DEDaF4 90&amp;rsquo;s kid Color Value Remark #97ECF1 #DFFDFF #BDB2FF #FAD1FA #FEC868 #F1F785 New kicks Color Value Remark #FD8A8A #FFCBCB #9EA1D4 #F1F7B5 #A8D1F1 #DFEBEB Pastel Blue Color Palettes Cotton Candy Cloud Color Value Remark #FAE7E8 #F2D7E8 #ECF8F7 #858EBC #D8BBD3 #D1EDEA Waterfall Color Value Remark #E5F8F8 #EEF6F2 #D6DFE8 #C2EBEF #A8CAD6 #D5E3E4 Beach towels Color Value Remark #C0E5E8 #EFECE6 #DAF4EF #DEEBEB #9EDCE1 #EFE4CB </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markdown flavors</title>
      <link>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/markdown/markdown_flavors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 22:09:48 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/markdown/markdown_flavors/</guid>
      <description>Markdown flavors Markdown flavors are variations or extensions of the original Markdown syntax, designed to offer additional functionality or slightly different syntax rules. Different platforms and applications often use their own custom Markdown flavors to suit their specific needs. Here are some common flavors of Markdown:&#xA;Standard Markdown&#xA;Developer: John Gruber Features: Basic features like headers, lists, links, and inline formatting. Notable: This is the original Markdown specification. CommonMark&#xA;Developer: Community effort led by John MacFarlane Features: A standardized and unambiguous version of Markdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markdown</title>
      <link>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/markdown/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 21:45:36 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaiseru1612.github.io/otamegane/en/blog/technical/markdown/markdown/</guid>
      <description>Introduction You may well have heard of Markdown, but it’s okay if you haven’t. The typical way that users first might encounter Markdown is through formatting text on internet message boards. You might have encountered it used on GitHub in readme files, at the very least. A professional use for Markdown is to write technical documentation. Technical writers have a dazzling array of options for producing their documentation. That’s why many writers opt for Markdown – it’s easy to use, and adaptable between different platforms (at least, in theory).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
